I'm leaving now.
What's with the leftovers,
does my food taste bad?
No, I'm just on a diet.
On a diet? It'll be fifty five dollars.
Don't lose too much weight,
or the wind will blow you away.
Right, as if...
Thanks a lot, see ya... Bye.
Haven't seen you in a year,
yet you still have an appetite.
Well, I'm full now.
It was very satisfying.
It makes you feel alive.
Do you think God will forgive us...
For what we did in the past?
Well, it depends which way you look at it.
What suddenly made you think like this?
You know travelling alone these few years,
boredom I guess...
It gets me thinking sometimes...
Your fried eggs and tomatoes
still taste like crap
No it doesn't.
If it tasted so bad, why did you finish it?
You didn't add soy sauce?
Who fries eggs with soy sauce?
Who doesn't fry eggs with soy sauce?
Let me fry some up for you...
I won't eat it.
Eat it. It's very good.
Wife
Excuse me, Excuse me please
Attention residents, please remain calm
In light of
the typhoon signal number 8 being hoisted
All ferry services have been stopped.
But officer, I have to go to a banquet.
So are the boats still running or not?
Officer, isn't that a boat coming?
That's the last ferry coming in.
Once it docks, it stays.
Come on...
Officer Hanson,
when will the ferry service resume?
Mrs. Fong,
I'm a policeman, not a weather man.
I can't answer that question.
Watch the news, everybody.
How can we watch the news now?
I have nowhere to spend the night,
what am I going to do?
Don't wait here,
if you can go home, go home.
If you're looking for a place to stay,
go look.
Alright now, stop hanging around here.
I'm in a hurry.
There's nothing I can do
There's still no answer
on Chairman Ma's phone.
Keep trying.
Did you listen carefully?
Well, fugitives are always on the run.
Last I heard he was nearby.
Sir, is there anything to eat around here?
There's a typhoon, sorry we're closing.
Thanks.
Baby, come here...
Come on, over here.
Come, baby.
Come here.
Come here, baby, come...
Baby... come, come to mom.
Baby... come, yeah.
Yeah... come here
Oh my god, I'm so sorry
I'll pay you back.
Do you have a needle and thread?
Yeah.
Are you here on holiday?
Aren't you bored, traveling alone and all?
I'm used to it. Being alone is convenient.
Well, we're stuck with a typhoon today,
pretty bad timing for a holiday
Since I'm here, I may as well enjoy myself.
I don't mind.
You know, you can speak to me in Cantonese
Ok.
Wow your bag's heavy...
Did you buy a lot of souvenirs?
It's a bowling ball.
You brought a bowling ball on your vacation?
I'm a bowling instructor.
Are restaurants here open during a typhoon?
There's one restaurant downstairs
that stays open despite the typhoon.
Just take a left downstairs,
walk down three blocks.
Turn right, take the shortcut
through the bushes and you're there.
How about this, I'll take you there.
But lunch is on you.
Damn it... It's a typhoon 8
and I'm still stuck here working.
Little Ming, since you're sitting so close,
why don't you crank up the radio
Turn it up you idiot...
So nobody's eating, big deal,
I'm still making my noodles
I got nothing to do anyway,
tell me, what else can I do?
Winds are expected to pick up
in speed within the next few hours
Good morning, Uncle G.
Good morning, Hiu wor
Morning, Little Ming
New boyfriend?
No, Mr. Bo is here on vacation.
Mr. Bo?
Mr. Bo...
Sparing some time for vacation, I see.
Let me introduce our specials for today
The abalone here is famous for...
No thanks, we'll have the usual please
What's the usual?
That would be fish ball noodles.
Make it five...
Have you found a place to stay yet?
With the typhoon going on, there won't be
a ferry leaving for a long time
I tell you what, I have a place for rent
that you can take up for the night
Just four hundred and fifty dollars
Think about it.
Fifty dollars for a bowl of noodles?
Are you trying to rob us?
The Hong Kong Observatory advises us
to stay indoors during the typhoon
I'm risking my life here...
If I get blown away,
who's gonna look after my restaurant?
Fine... Same price for you
And I'll waive his 10% service charge.
Damn it. Now I'm losing money.
You don't look like a bowling instructor
whichever way I look at you
Well you don't like a police officer either.
What are you on about?
All female cops in western films
look just like her...
It was Hiu Wor's childhood dream
to become a police officer. How righteous.
Well
I wouldn't say it was my! Childhood dream.
Certain things just require people
who care to do the job
Exactly...
Hiu wor and I are just those type of people
Whatever your complaints are, whether it
involves hygiene, transportation or housing
Even as small as the discoloration of
toilet paper in public bathrooms,
The lack of garbage cans
or the lack of tourist information posts
Just say a word,
and I'll have it reported immediately
I pay special attention to those
who are weak and less fortunate
People like you can't protect yourself
and lack self-righteousness
And that's where Hiu wor and I come in.
Come on,
we're not the only ones that can help
Defending justice and upholding society
is everyone's responsibility
Here let's eat
Anything else you need?
Chopsticks
Oh, yes
A speedboat in High Island
was overturned by a massive tidal wave.
Everyone on board is missing.
The marine police have uncovered a large
quantity of US Dollars on the abandoned vessel
Preliminary investigations reveal
a possible connection
with a robbery of a money
exchange bureau in Tsim Sha Tsui last week.
Police are investigating three male suspects
of Chinese nationality.
Eat your noodles.
This is the police,
please take out your ID cards
You want to check my ID
while I'm eating noodles?
Why do you want to check my ID?
Excuse me, sir.
Can I please see some identification?
Excuse me, sir. Can I please see...
My shoe...
What the hell?
Are you alright?
Can you please do me one more favour?
Can you come with me
to the police station to file a statement?
Little Ming, where's my... my restaurant?
I know it's gone... Why didn't you mediate?
I knew you wouldn't
Alright let's go for a foot massage.
How about you massage it for me?
Don't be shy, come on...
I don't bite. It's right here.
Wrong. This 'mouth' character is too big.
The character for 'mouth' can't be bigger
than the character for 'eat'.
Otherwise you wouldn't be able
to fit the food into your mouth.
Why would you have such a big mouth to eat?
A little mouth is good for eating.
Just write it smaller.
Smaller...
Little Kin,
are you finished with your homework yet?
Your mother is back.
Let's go home for dinner.
Okay okay, coming
Alldone... Mommy
Finish the rest of it when you get home.
Did you ask Tarzan
for help with your homework?
Yes, it's all done. Good boy.
Here, vegetables.
How much?
Just take it, I'll tell you tomorrow.
Thankyou. Bye. Bye.
Mom, Tarzan bullied me.
What are you talking about?
Who bullied you?
Hello?
Commissioner Yu
No problem,
just sign your name and you can go Mr. Bo.
Thank you, thank you.
Attention...
Headquarters is now verifying our suspects
There's a 90% chance we caught the guys
involved in the Tsim Sha Tsui robbery last week.
Good work... You smart girl...
I've been on the police force for 1 O years
and I've never cracked a big case.
You've been at it for two years
and already you've solved a major case...
No, it was all Mr. Bo,
couldn't have done it without him.
Just call me Bo.
One against three?
You've been eating 'night congee'.
Is that a midnight snack?
It's slang for you've been training
Well...
Let me introduce myself. I'm Grant Gong.
I represent the Outlying Islands district.
Thank you for helping us solve our case.
I'll be nominating you
for the 'Good Citizens' Award
Well, I can't fight Kung Fu, but I do know
one or two things about making Kung Fu tea
Come let's all have some tea
to celebrate. Come
Where's the head?
Can anyone recognize the person
who killed Chairman Ma?
There are four of you, four pairs of eyes
and nobody caught a glimpse of his face?
He was very quick.
Very quick?
Were you drunk?
He was carrying a bag.
What kind of bag?
What kind? What colour was it?
Boss, something has happened to Chairman Ma
They took his head.
Find his head...
We have to preserve his whole body...
Yes, boss.
Keep a few people here
to watch Chairman Ma.
The others, follow me.
No matter what,
we must find Chairman Ma's head.
Let's go... wake up...
Come and taste my Kung Fu tea
Here, this is yours
Here you go, kiddo
Thanks
Cheers everybody
Thank you.
There are loads more convicts here,
why don't you catch
them all since you're all that
Wanted: Timothy Ma
Mr. Good Citizen
How long have you been in Hong Kong?
Two days.
What is your business on this island?
I'm on vacation.
Where are you staying?
I just checked out
I already asked.
Do you know how to write the symbol
for 'death' in complex characters?
Tarzan.
There is no difference between 'death'
in complex or simplified characters
Catching criminals are for those
who have undergone professional training.
A bit of Kung Fu is not gonna
take you anywhere
What?
You think you're a cat with nine lives?
Are we clear?
The officer cannot hear you,
I said, are we clear...
I can't hear you, speak up...
Tarzan, what the hell is your problem?
Did you pop the wrong pills today?
No, Hiu wor.
This type of guy, these brutes.
They're bullies.
They misuse their strength.
They're dangerous. Keep your distance, ok?
And also,
if there's anything out of the ordinary
Speak up...
Get ready for dinner...
Okay.
Maggie, could you please add another place
and cook five extra bowls of rice
I made the rice already.
Come on, please.
Grant Gong and I will help you.
I don't have time.
Here, take my seat
We'll be eating very shortly
Waste of breath.
You're really pathetic.
I won't even let anyone sit down.
And you let them push you around.
You're terrible.
Sir, there are no more rooms left to rent.
Sit down.
No, boss.
You guys go look that way,
we'll go this way. Let's go.
He's like the plague,
even the light is broken.
Stop checking yourself out. You'll never
be as good-looking as me. Now move over.
Fix the light.
Call the electrician to come fix it.
You're crazy. I can fix it myself.
Be careful.
Move over... watch this...
Wow, that was one strong kick.
Brother, are you alright?
Ambush... He's attacking the police...
Hey, what are you doing?
I feel much better, all of a sudden
What? Something wrong?
Not bad.
Come on, it's dinnertime.
You look violent even when you eat?
Hey kid,
just because you don't want yours...
Doesn't mean you
should give him mine as well.
It's alright.
I'll just ask Maggie to cook more food.
Maggie left.
Are you messing with me?
Is the taste too plain?
No, it's okay.
It's been a long time since
I've eaten such spicy and tasty vegetables.
You can't eat spicy foods?
Who says I can't?
If you can't take it, spit it out.
I'm full... I'm full...
So how was your first meal at the jailhouse?
Very fulfilling.
Well, eating it once is enough.
As for those three thieves, they'll be
eating it for a long time to come...
As for you, kiddo. Lucky Bo was there
Next time something like this happens again,
you must report it to me immediately.
It was very dangerous.
I'm a police officer, why would I be scared?
That's exactly what I feared,
that you're not afraid of anything...
If only you had gone with your mother
to Canada, everything would've been fine.
But no, you had to become a police officer.
She has a family of her own,
I don't want to get in their way.
I was born and bred here,
I mean, I speak Cantonese.
This is my home, why should I leave?
What about you? Where's your home?
Yeah.
I come from the grasslands.
I don't have any more family.
Oh I know, you must be...
One of those guys
who rides his horse everywhere.
Kind of like a shepherd right?
Something like that.
...es.
Actually, we're just like you.
We're orphans too.
But orphans plus orphan equal family.
...es.
Eat... It's very good.
Look Uncle G, let's cut the nonsense
Just find me a place that's cheap,
nice and spacious.
Alright, I'll be waiting for your reply
I'll find you a place to live very soon.
Here, drink some tea.
Don't worry,
I won't charge you a commission.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to Hiu Wor
Happy birthday to you...
Happy Birthday...
Thank you.
I chose this cake myself.
Make a wish about me okay.
Whatever.
Good...
Sorry you had to do the dishes with me.
Well I had a part in eating,
so I have a part in cleaning.
You got that right.
Oh by the way,
thank you for cooperating with the police.
Do you have to be so cool?
You're cuter when you eat.
You almost died back there.
Weren't you even a little scared?
Yeah.
But as a cop, you have to face your fears.
It's our responsibility.
Hey, what's that?
A wolf's tooth.
You like wolves?
I respect them.
They are the guardian spirits of the plains.
We nomads believe that when we die...
the wolf can guide our spirits to heaven.
What, so you worried about going to hell?
Maybe.
Come on, you're definitely going to heaven.
You're a good person.
Thanks.
You know,
I have a more practical guardian angel.
You.
Why don't I teach you
how to protect yourself?
Are you kidding,
I should teach you a few moves or two.
What are you doing?
I'll arrest you for police harassment.
I shall arrest you first...
When you're done with your cake, leave...
This is a police station,
or did you think it was a resort?
Let's go, noise complaint.
Come on, let's go.
Where?
Next to Tin Hau Temple Road.
Mrs. Robinson again?
Who else?
What were you doing with him?
Nothing, none of your business.
Thanks for helping out, Uncle G
Lunch is on me
Alright, bye.
Bo, alright. Come here.
I found you two places.
Both are in Tung Wan.
Both are two hundred fifty.
One has a TV the other one doesn't.
Thanks.
Stop... Stop...
Stop...
Give it to me...
Why did you grab my bag?
Why are you running away?
I'm going home.
Hiu wor
did you like the birthday' gift I gave you?
Yes thanks, but next time,
don't waste your money.
It's not a waste, as long as you liked it.
So did you like it?
Hey...
So what's the matter Mrs. Robinson?
Who's disturbing you tonight?
Those dogs over there
have been barking all night. I can't sleep...
Go and poison them for me...
Mrs. Robinson, calm down now.
We'll take care of it.
You'll take care of it...
You better take care of it
or else I'll report you...
So damn troublesome.
Dogs are animals, they bark,
what does she expect?
They only bark when there are strangers.
Hiu wor, did you see the present yet?
Did you like it?
What's the matter with you? What's going on?
What are all of you doing here together?
We're just avoiding the rain officer.
What's on the ground?
Stand over there
I said stand over there
Stand right there...
Don't move...
Boss
Have you found Chairman Ma's head yet?
Not yet, but Jellyfish is onto him.
You must find Chairman Ma's head.
I know, Boss.
But...
Chairman Ma
is now inside the police station.
What?
They found Chairman Ma's body
and brought him to the station.
You idiot... Chairman Ma can not stay
overnight at the police station...
You have to get him out.
Put the bag down.
Seriously Hanson,
we've been brothers for over 1 O years now.
You have to believe me on this one.
I really saw Bo...
Who beat you guys up?
Hiu wor, did you see Bo?
No.
Grant Gong
This case definitely involves Bo.
Why?
When I was on-site, I saw Bo's shadow.
You saw Bo's shadow?
No seriously.
Think about it.
The two of us beat up three guys.
So who beat up these two?
Who has the best Kung Fu on the island...
and who else would come back to save her
You see, he couldn't have known
where to go to save her
Unless, he knew there was something going on
But he couldn't have known
what was going on there.
Unless he had something to do with it.
I agree.
Where's the proof?
I want to file a report...
What's the problem?
Madam, I've been beaten.
Calm down and speak slowly
What's the problem...
One at a time, what's the issue?
Let him go...
Don't mess with me.
I just want to take the body away.
Hold your fire, it's gasoline...
Don't move... Don't move...
Stay calm
Let go...
Open the lock... Hurry up...
Hurry up...
Where's the body?
Hey, come help
Hold your fire, it's gasoline...
Don't move... Get down...
Get down... don't move...
Officer Hanson...
Tarzan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're all okay right?
No, we're fine.
What's wrong?
Do I look bad?
You look great...
You were brave as ever today.
Special report,
Typhoon Bo is steering away from Hong Kong.
The Hong Kong Observatory
has lowered the signal to a signal 3.
All transportation will resume
their normal operations shortly.
Morning, sir.
Is everyone here?
Everyone is here sir.
Let's go
Yes, sir...
At this point, nobody's happy.
Including myself.
Now what we need to do is
bring this murderer to justice.
Our sources tell us that
this case involves
an international drug ring.
The deceased is Timothy Ma,
also known as Chairman Ma.
He is the crime syndicate mastermind,
and is wanted by international authorities.
Right now,
his body is intact and his head is missing.
Which means,
the murderer could be on the run
with his head and still on this island
Involved in this case is another person
Who is avengingt...
Timothy Ma's death
I have reason to believe that...
The gang who came into the police station
to steal his body
is linked to Chairman Ma's wife.
Two officers
were injured during the incident
One hour later, an attack occurred
at the local police station.
One officer was killed.
Special report:
A suspected murder
was uncovered in the Outlying Islands
The Marine Police are on their way to the
crime scene to assist further investigation.
You over there...
Check it again...
Did you find anything? Negative.
What's up Officer?
Freeze...
Don't move...
Police... Stop...
Dispatch, suspect found,
black shirt, black pants...
Central Command,
please verify ID number K 782021 (6)
Timothy Ma's wife
Miho Sasaki
While Timothy Ma was on the run,
She took control of the crime syndicate.
Unfortunately,
we have no evidence against this woman
because her record is cleaner than yours.
ID card
Hurry up.
What's inside the bag?
Open it, let me have a look.
Where do you live?
I live in Kowloon.
So did you bring it or not?
We need to handle this now.
Hurry up and find Timothy Ma's murderer.
Prevent any and all confrontation.
Sir
I suspect someone.
Attention all units...
We have a suspect; male
30s, medium build
short, dark brown hair,
speaks fluent Putonghua
wearing army green jacket and black trousers
You in the green jacket...
stay right there... Don't move...
The guy in green, freeze...
Don't move, now put down your bag
Did you hear me?
Putdown the bag... Faster...
Put down your bag...
Don't move... Don't move...
Both hands on your head.
Don't move.
Let's go... Let's go... Let's go...
Yes, sir...
Are you in a hurry to leave?
The boat is here.
Bo Tong Lam
If you did not break the law,
you will definitely catch this ferry.
Open the bag
I said, open the bag.
Don't move...
Kid
Let's go
Bo
Last night, Officer Hanson...
My condolences.
Can you answer a question for me?
Last night, the person
who saved me at Tin Hau Temple Road...
Was that you?
No
Goodbye
Can I borrow your phone?
Call me.
Ok.
Bye.
Bye
Hello?
Fat wing
Boss
Where is he?
I'm watching him.
Don't let him escape
He won't escape.
How much longer before the boat arrives?
Did you hear me? How much longer...
Fat wing
Fat wing, say something...
I asked you how much longer...
About half and hour
I want you to return my husband's head.
I'll give you one day to leave Hong Kong.
You haven't slept all night, are you tired?
Do you think you'll be alive tomorrow?
I ask myself the same question everyday,
tomorrow...
Will I still be alive?
Don't worry
Everything will come to an end soon.
Fat wing
Help, help...
I'm in here...
Help him out.
No need to help me.
Hurry up, get the guy
in the green jacket with the bag.
Hurry up... Hurry...
Hello?
Hey kid,
Our colleagues
have discovered Timothy Ma's killer.
Hey you there?
Who is it?
We suspect it's Bo
Officers found Timothy Ma's head
inside a bowling ball.
He just escaped.
Commissioner Yu wants you back
at the station immediately
Drive
Please lend me your phone.
How was your vacation?
Pretty good.
I heard a birthday song and made a wish.
It's a holiday, you should be happy.
Bo
Hiu wor
Hello
I'm sorry, I'm keeping you
from returning to the Police Station
With all the bad you've done, it's only
a matter of time before we get you...
What about your friend then?
He killed Chairman Ma, will you arrest him?
I will arrest anyone that breaks the law.
Your friend is here,
shall I allow you to arrest him first?
How many assailants do you think
he can take on?
Fifty or a hundred?
Bo...
Quick... Get up... Bo...
Bo, run...
Bo...
Bo, get up...
Hurry, get up Bo...
Bo...
Let me show you how it feels to be beheaded...
Yesterday...
was the...
...happiest day of my life,
it was also my birthday
Eventually, he left
just like the typhoon,
leaving nothing behind
nobody knows
why he took Chairman Ma's head.
Some say it's a native custom
Until one day, I discovered a news story.
One year ago,
a nurse from a volunteer organization
was abducted by drug dealers while treating
a patient along the Thai-Burma border.
Chairman Ma took her hostage
and demanded the local government
to release his party members from jail.
In the end, the negotiations fell apart.
Afterwards,
I searched for more old news articles
which were possibly related to him.
Hey there...
Long time no see.
I've been busy,
I hardly come this way nowadays
Shredded beef, less rice?
To go please, thanks.
Shredded beef, less rice
Fifty-Five dollars
What's with the leftovers,
does my food taste bad?
No, I'm just on a diet.
On a diet?
It'll be fifty five dollars
Don't lose too much weight,
or the wind will blow you away,
Right, as if...
Ok, thanks, bye bye.